(Sheldon:)Damn you, WalletNook.com.
(Leonard:)Problem?
(Sheldon:)The online description
was completely misleading.
(Sheldon:)They said eight slots plus removable ID.
(Sheldon:)To any rational person,
that would mean room for nine cards.
(Sheldon:)But they don't tell you,
the removable ID takes up one slot.
(Sheldon:)It's a nightmare.
(Leonard:)Okay, now, do you really need...
(Leonard:)...the honorary Justice League
of America membership card?
(Sheldon:)It's been in every wallet
I've owned since I was 5.
(Leonard:)Why?
It says, "Keep this on your person
at all times."
[KNOCK ON DOOR]
(Sheldon:)It's right here, under Batman's signature.
(Raj:)And this is Leonard
and Sheldon's apartment.
[CHUCKLES]
Guess whose parents just got broadband.
Leonard, may I present, live from New Delhi,
Dr. and Mrs. V. M. Koothrappali?
(Leonard:)Hi.
Tilt up the camera.
I'm looking at his crotch.